smartnsdc.org 2017-05-03

# SMART - Skill Management & Accreditation of Training Centre

#### Privacy Policy

This website does not automatically capture any specific personal information from you (like name, phone number or e-mail address), that allows us to identify you individually. You can visit this Site, without revealing, Personal Information, unless you choose to provide such information. Any Personal information collected shall be used only for the stated purpose .We do not collect personal information for any purpose other than to respond to you (for example, to respond to your queries ). If you choose to provide us with personal information like filling out a Contact Us form with an e-mail address or postal address, and submitting it to us through the website, we use that information to respond to your message, and to help you get the information you have requested. Any information provided to this website will be protected from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Our website never collects information or creates individual profiles for commercial marketing. While you must provide an e-mail address for a localised response to any incoming questions or comments to us, we recommend that you do NOT include any other personal information.

This site may contain links to other sites whose data protection and privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of these other websites and encourage you to consult the privacy notices of those sites.
